(Bernadette:)because no one wants you
to express yours.
(Bernadette:)Oh, Amy, I'm so sorry.
(Bernadette:)That was over the line.
(Amy:)You have a nice night.
(Bernadette:)Please don't go.
(Bernadette:)Up until my vicious attack,
you were the one in the wrong.
(Sheldon:)Here you go, Doctor.
(Sheldon:)Red Zinger
with one teaspoon of honey.
(Man with Flowers:)Thank you.
Neat Star Trek mug.
(Man:)I actually have
one of the phasers
(Man:)from the original TV show.
(Raj:)Oh, cool.
(Howard:)How'd you get that?
(Man:)Oh, easy, Gene Roddenberry
needed a vasectomy.
(Sehldon:)Wait a minute.
(Sehldon:)You've snipped
Gene Roddenberry's vas deferens?
(Leonard:)Yes.
(Howard:)Wow, he really went
where no man has gone before.
(Man:)I don't like to brag,
but, uh, you see,
(Man:)I'm kind of the doctor
to the stars' urinary tracts.
ALL:
Wow.